这些价格不菲
Ok, these were unbelievably expensive,
而且我知道他很快就穿不下  但我实在无法抗拒
and I know he's gonna grow out of them in like, 20 minutes, but I couldn't resist
看看这些
Look at these.
本
Hey, Ben.
天呐
Oh, my God
是不是给他的压力太大了
Was that too much pressure for him?
-他已经饿了吗  -我想是的
- Is he hungry already? - I guess so.
你知道吗
You know, it's....
球鞋真的很有趣  我马上就回来
Something funny about sneakers. I'll be right back.
我也要一个
I gotta get one too.
你们在干什么
Hey, what are you guys doing?
我们只是来看看汤匙
We're just hanging out by the spoons.
调羹
Ladle?
你们成熟一点好吗
Will you guys grow up?
这是世上最自然美丽的
This is the most nature beautiful thing in the world.
我们知道  但是有个婴儿在吸它
Yeah, we know. But there's a baby sucking on it.
这是我儿子享用午餐  这是常事  你们最好习惯
This is my son having lunch, okay? It'll happen a lot, so you have to get used to it.
如果你们感到不自在  发问就好
Now if you have any problem with it, if you're uncomfortable, just ask questions.
卡罗尔不介意的
Carol's fine with it, now come on.
-卡罗尔  -卡罗尔
- Carol? - Carol?
我想问问  乔伊能不能问关于哺乳的问题
I was just wondering if Joey could ask you a question about breast-feeding?
可以
Sure.
会不会痛
Does it hurt?
刚开始会  现在不会了
It did at first, but not anymore.
钱德勒呢
Chandler?
你能多久喂一次
So, how often can you do it?
他要多久就喂多少
As much as he needs.
我想到了一个问题
Okay, I got one, I got one.
如果他对一个吹气  另一个会不会变大
If he blows into one, does the other one get bigger?
瑞秋  还有松糕吗
Rachel, do you have any muffins left?
还有  不过我忘记是哪一种了
Yeah, I forget which ones.
你太忙了  没关系  我去拿
Oh, you're busy, that's ok, I'll get it.
-还有谁要吗  -不用了  谢谢.
- Anyone else want one? - No, thanks.
你的围裙松了  我帮你系好
Oh, you're losin' your apron here, let me get it.
-好了  -多谢
- There you go. - Thank you.
臭婆娘好过分
What a bitch.
大家听我说
Oh, listen, you guys.
我有朋友在布明岱尔百货上班  明天辞职
I have this friend at Bloomingdales who's quitting tomorrow
他想要花掉他的折扣优待
and he wants to abuse his discount.
谁想跟我去捡便宜
So, anyone want to come with me and take advantage of it?
我不行  我要带我奶奶去看兽医
I can't, I have to take my grandmother to the vet.
-好吧  我跟你去  -太好了
- Okay, I'll go with you. - Great.
-亲爱的  -甜心
- Hi, honey. - Hey, sweetums.
大家好
And hello to the rest.
莫妮卡  你在干什么
Monica, what're you doin'?
你不能跟她去逛百货  瑞秋怎么办
You can't go shopping with her. What about Rachel?
会有问题  对不对
It's gonna be a problem, isn't it?
你想啊  你要跟朱莉去布明岱尔
Come on, you're going to Bloomingdale's with Julie.
就像是到瑞秋家中偷汉子
It's like cheating on Rachel in her house of worship.
她会宰了你
Monica, she will kill you.
她会宰了你  就像宰街上的流浪狗
She will kill you like a dog in the street.
朱莉说你们明天要去逛街
So Jules tells me you guys are going shopping tomorrow.
其实没有什么
It's actually not that big a deal.
对我很重要  非常重要  莫妮卡
It's a big deal to me. This is great, Monica.
我非常感激你这么做
I really appreciate this.
别客气
You're welcome.
碧欧泉男士香水
Bijan for men?
-安娜贝尔  -乔伊
- Hey, Annabel. - Hey, Joey.
-听说过新来的人吗  -谁
- Did you hear about the new guy? - Who?
没人知道他的名字  我们女生都叫他原野奇侠
Nobody knows his name. Me and the girls call him "The Hombre Man. "
原野奇侠
Hombre?
他到我这一区干什么
What's he doing in my section?
我想他不知道
I guess he doesn't know.
马上就知道了
Well, he's gonna.
待会见
I'll see you a little later, okay?
你好吗
Hey, how you doing?
早
Mornin'.
听着  我知道你是新来的
Listen, I know you're new...
但众所周知这附近的一切
... but it's kind of understood that everything
从青年男装部到电梯都是我的地盘
from young men's to the escalator is my territory.
-你的地盘  -对
- "Your territory"? -Yes.
-碧欧泉男士香水  -不  谢了
- Bijan for men? - No, thanks.
原野奇侠
Hombre?
好吧
Yeah, all right.
你刚才说什么
You were saying?
菲比  听着  你跟我逛了一整天街买东西
Phoebe, listen. You were with me, and we were shopping all day.
-什么  -我们买了东西  还吃了午餐
- What? - We were shopping and we had lunch.
好吧  我吃了什么
Oh, all right. What did I have?
-你吃的沙拉  -难怪我觉得没吃饱
- You had a salad. - No wonder I don't feel full.
姑娘们  怎么了
Hey, guys, What's up?
我整天都跟摩妮卡买东西  还吃了沙拉
I went shopping with Monica all day and I had a salad.
很好  菲比  你们买了什么
Good, Pheebs. What'd you buy?
我们买了
We went shopping for....
买了
For....
买了皮毛
For fur.
你去买了皮毛
You went shopping for fur?
然后我发现我反对买皮毛
And then I realized that l'm against that.
于是我们买了一些
So then we bought some....
乳房
Boobs.
你买了乳房
You bought boobs?
胸罩
Bras.
我们买了胸罩
We bought bras.
碧欧泉男士香水
Bijan for men?
碧欧泉
Bijan for....
安娜贝尔
Hey, Annabel.
下了班要不要去喝咖啡
Listen, I was wondering if after work we could grab a cup of coffee?
我已经有约了
Actually, I sort of have plans.
准备好了吗  安娜贝尔
You ready, Annabel?
好了
You bet.
以后再约吧
Maybe some other time.
我又不是没被喷香水的牛仔抢过妹子
It's not the first time I lost a girl to a cowboy spraying cologne.
碧欧泉男士香水
Bijan for men?
Bijan for men
这是滑稽小丑
Okay. And this is Funny Clown.
只有睡过午觉才可以给他玩
Funny Clown is only for after his naps,
否则他会睡不着
not before his naps or he won't sleep.
卡罗尔  我带过他  我们玩得很高兴
Carol, we've been through this before, ok? We have a good time.
我们又笑又玩  如同父子
We laugh, we play. It's like we're father and son.
罗斯很会带他
Honey, relax. Ross is great with him.
别这么惊讶  我很可亲
Don't look so surprised. I'm a lovely person.
好可爱
This is so cute.
我为他买的
I got that for him.
我的妈妈们爱我
"My Mommies Love Me."
真聪明
That's clever.
喂  你好  朱
Hello. Oh, hi, Jul....
你好  犹太人
Hi, Jew.
好的  可以
Okay, sure.
很好  到时见  再见
That'd be great. See you then. Bye.
你刚才是不是说  "你好  犹太人"
Did you just say, " Hi, Jew"?
对  没错
Yes, I did.
那是我的犹太朋友艾迪·莫斯考维兹
That was my friend Eddie Moskowitz.
他很喜欢这称呼  能加强他的信仰
Yeah, he likes it. Reaffirms his faith.
本  吃晚餐了
Ben, dinner.
谢谢  菲比阿姨
Thanks, Aunt Pheebs.
你没有用微波炉吧
Hey, you didn't microwave that, did you,
不应该这样处理母乳
because it's breast milk, and you're not supposed to do that.
切  我想我知道如何加热母乳
Duh, I think I know how to heat breast milk.
好了
Ok.
你做了什么
What did you just do
我舔了我的手臂  怎么样
I licked my arm, what?
那是母乳
It's breast milk.
那又怎样
So?
菲比  那是从另一个人身上挤出的汁
Phoebe, that is juice squeezed from a person.
-有什么了不起  -不
- What is the big deal? - No.
你又干了些什么
What did you just do?
大家能不能别再喝母乳了
Can people stop drinking the breast milk?
-你连尝都不尝  -不尝
- You won't even taste it? - No.
不能假装那是牛奶吗
Not even if you just pretend it's milk?
就算卡罗尔的乳房贴了寻人广告都不行
Not even if Carol's breast had a picture of a missing child on it.
大家到哪里去了
Where is everybody?
带本去公园了  你去哪里了
They took Ben to the park. Where have you been?
出去了
Just out.
吃了午餐  只有我一个人  自己度过了美好时光
Had some lunch. Just me. A little quality time with me.
-谢谢你的夹克  -没问题.
- Thanks for your jacket. - Oh, no problem.
你也可以借去穿
You can borrow it, by the way.
-你的钥匙  亲爱的  -好
- Here are your keys, honey. - I got it.
莫妮卡
Mon.
如果你一个人吃午餐  怎么会要53块
If you were at lunch alone, how come it cost you $53?
你知道有什么可能吗
You know what probably happened?
一定有人偷了我的信用卡
Someone must has stolen my credit card.
然后把收据放回你口袋
And sorta just put the receipt back in your pocket?
这个问题问得非常非常好
That is an excellent, excellent question.
相当厉害
That is excellent.
莫妮卡  你和谁在一起  和谁一起吃的午饭
Monica, what's with you? Who did you have lunch with?
-朱蒂  -谁
- Judy. - Who?
-朱莉  -什么
- Julie. - What?
裘迪
Jody.
你跟朱莉在一起
You were with Julie?
刚开始我只是想对她友善点
Look, when it started, I was just trying to be nice to her...
因为她是我哥哥的女友
... because she was my brother's girlfriend.
然后就顺理成章
And then one thing led to another...
在我搞明白之前  我们就
...and before I knew it, we were...
逛街了
...shopping.
我的天
Oh, my God.
等等  我们只做了一次
Wait, we only did it once.
对我没有任何意义
It didn't meant anything to me.
好吧
Right. Sure.
瑞秋  我惦记的一直都是你
Really, Rachel, I was thinking of you the whole time.
对不起  好吗  我不希望你知道的
Look, I'm sorry, all right? I never meant for you to find out.
拜托  你希望被逮到才是的
Oh, please. Please You wanted to get caught.
不是这样的
That is not true.
所以你不小心留收据在这里
So you just happened to leave it in here?
你觉得我会这么笨吗
Did it ever occur to you that I might just be that stupid?
好  我必须知道一件事
Ok, Monica. I just have to know one thing.
你有没有跟她去布明岱尔
Did you go with her to Bloomingdale's?
好吧  好吧
Okay, okay.
我现在不能跟你在一起了
Okay, I just really need to not be with you right now.
你是哪位
Hi, who's this?
琼安  瑞秋在吗  我是摩妮卡
Hi, Joanne. Is Rachel working? It's Monica.
我知道我做了错事
Yes, I know I did a horrible thing.
琼安  事情没这么简单  好吗
Joanne, it's not as simple as all that, okay?
不  我才不在乎史蒂夫怎么想  你好  史蒂夫
No, I don't care what Steve thinks. Hi, Steve.
情况如何
How did we do?
我尝了本的奶  罗斯就发火了
I tasted Ben's milk and Ross freaked out.
我没有发火
I did not freak out.
-你为什么发火  -因为那是母乳
- Why'd you freak out? - Because it's breast milk.
很呕心
It's gross.
我的奶水很呕心
My breast milk is gross?
有好戏看了
This should be fun.
这没什么不对
No, no, Carol. There's nothing wrong with it.
我只是不认为母乳是给大人喝的
I just don't think breast milk is for adults.
当然装母乳的容器很吸引大人与小孩
Of course, the packaging does appeal to grownups and kids.
罗斯  别傻了  我试过  没什么
Ross, you're being silly. I've tried it, it's no big deal.
快尝尝
Come on. Just taste it.
不行
That would be no.
-尝尝吧  很天然  -试试  -不
- Come on. It's natural. - Try it. - No.
又不难吃
It doesn't taste bad.
有一点甜  很像...
Yeah, it tastes kind of sweet. Sort of like....
-像什么  -哈密瓜汁
- Like what? - Cantaloupe juice.
没错
Exactly.
你尝过了
You've tasted it.
Oh, you've tasted it.
你再怎么重复这句话  也不会改变事实
You can keep saying it, but it won't stop being true.
把奶瓶给我
Give me the bottle.
把毛巾给我
Get me the towel.
你好
Howdy.
给我一盒果汁
Give me a box of juice.
他们把我调到原野奇侠了
Well, they switched me over to Hombre.
也许是因为你的穿着
Maybe it's because of the way you're dressed.
或因为那家伙表现太好了
Or maybe it's because this guy's doing so good
他们要增加人手
they wanna put more people on it.
你该见识一下  钱德勒  那家伙一天用掉两瓶
You should see this guy, Chandler, he goes through two bottles a day.
你在乎什么
What do you care?
你是个演员  这只是你的副业
You're an actor. This is your day job.
对你来说毫无意义
This isn't supposed to mean anything to you.
我知道  但我本来是最棒的
I know, but I was the best.
我喜欢当最棒的
You know? I liked being the best.
也许我应该退出江湖
I don't know.Maybe I should get out of the game.
厨具部门需要有人切乳酪
They need guys up in housewares to serve cheese.
假如你这么做了
Say you do that.
迟早会有乳酪切得比你好的人出现
Sooner or later, somebody will come along that slices a better cheddar.
那时候你要逃到哪里
Then where you gonna run?
也许你说得对
Yeah. I guess you're right.
我说的当然对了
You're damn right I'm right.
我说你应该拿出男子汉气概
I say you show him what you're made of.
我说你该坚守阵地
I say you stand your ground.
我说你让他知道你是内衣部西边最狠的原野奇侠
I say you show him that you are the baddest hombre west of the lingerie.
-就这么定了  -好的
- I'm gonna do it. - All right.
现在去找猫咪小姐  她会介绍个好妓女给你
Now, go see Miss Kitty and she'll fix you up with a nice hooker.
我不知道该说什么
I don't know what else to say.
很好  因为我也不会听
Well that works out good, because I'm not listening.
我很有负罪感  真的
I feel terrible. I really do.
对不起  我的背弄伤你的刀了吗
I'm sorry. Did my back hurt your knife?
瑞秋
Rachel,
就算我跟她交朋友  一起去逛街
say that I'm friends with her, we spend some time together.
-有那么糟吗  -有
- Is that so terrible? - Yes.
-到那么严重的地步吗  -是的  你还不懂吗
- It's that terrible? - Yes. Monica, you don't get it.
她偷走我的男人已经够糟了
It's bad enough she stole the guy...
他可能是我的真命天子
...who might be the person I'm supposed to be with.
但现在
But now...
她竟然
...she's actually....
现在她竟然连你也抢走了
But now she's actually stealing you.
我  你在胡说什么
Me? What are you talking about?
没人能把我从你那里抢走
Nobody could steal me from you.
我和她交朋友不会影响我和你的感情
Because I'm friends with her doesn't make me any less friends with you.
亲爱的  你是我的
Honey, I mean, you're my....
我们是
And we're....
-我爱你  -我也爱你
- Oh, I love you. - I love you too.
喂  我知道这事和我完全无关
You guys, I know that this really doesn't have anything to do with me.
但我也爱你们
But I love you guys, too.
我很需要纸巾
I really needed that.
我知道现在
Look, I know that you're in a place right now
你恨透了朱莉
where you really need to hate Julie's guts,
但是她没有做错什么
But she didn't do anything wrong.
她只是认识了一个男生  现在他们在交往
She's just a girl who met a guy, and now they go out.
我想如果你给她一个机会  你会喜欢她的
I think that if you gave her a chance, you'd like her.
你愿意给她一个机会吗
Will you give it a chance?
为了我
For me?
我愿意为你做任何事  你知道的
I'd do anything for you, you know that.
我什么都愿意为你做
I'd do anything for you.
等我  等我
Wait, wait, wait.
早
Mornin'.
我说  早
I said, mornin'.
我听见了
I heard you.
好的  各位  我要开门了
All right, everybody. I'm opening the doors.
你们准备好了吗
You boys ready?
好了
Ready.
我也好了
Yeah, l'm ready.
你这个白痴  你这个蠢牛仔
You idiot. You stupid cowboy.
你弄瞎我了  我要告你
You've blinded me. I'm suing.
天啊  陶德  你在搞什么鬼
Oh, my God, Todd. What the hell did you do?
对不起  我真是笨手笨脚
Sorry. I'm such a doofus.
对不起  非常对不起
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
老天  发生什么事了
My God, what happened?
这些菜鸟  都撑不了很久
These new kids, they never last.
迟早都会
Sooner or later they all...
歇菜
...stop lasting.
我们去喝杯咖啡怎么样
Listen. What do you say I buy you that cup of coffee now?
好的
Sure.
-那  -那
- So...  - So...
我想我们应该多接触
I just thought the two of us should hang out for a bit.
你知道的  我们从来没有真正交谈过
I mean, you know, we've never really talked.
我想你知道  我们俩在一起很尴尬
I guess you'd know that, being one of the two of us, all right?
我知道
I know.
我也许不该告诉你
I probably shouldn't even tell you this...
但是我真的完全被你的风采盖住了
... but l'm pretty much totally intimidated by you.
真的
Really?
我
Me?
你在开玩笑吗
Oh, my God, are you kidding?
罗斯还是对你很着迷
Ross is so crazy about you...
我真的希望你喜欢我
...and I really wanted you to like me, and l....
也许我只是胡思乱想
It's probably me just being totally paranoid...
但我好像觉得你不喜欢我
...but I kind of got the feeling that maybe you don't.
你不是完全胡思乱想
Well, you're not totally paranoid.
是这样  天呐
Okay, god.
当你和罗斯刚开始交往时
When you and Ross first started going out...
我真的很难过
...it was really hard for me...
有太多理由让我不喜欢你
...for many reasons of which I'm not gonna bore you with now.
可...
But...
但我看到他多么快乐  你们在一起是多么相配
I see how happy he is and how good you guys are together.
摩妮卡一直说你有多好
And Monica's always saying how nice you are...
我真讨厌她说得对
...and God, I hate it when she's right.
谢谢
Thanks.
你想不想一起去看电影或出去玩
Listen. Would you like to go to a movie sometime or something?
这样很好  我很乐意
Yeah, that'd be great. I'd love it.
我也是
I'd love it too.
该死  我得要走了
Shoot, I gotta go.
-以后再聊  -好的  朱莉
- So I'll talk to you later. - All right, Julie.
-再见  -再见
- Bye.  - Bye.
心机婊
What a manipulative bitch.
还不错
Not bad.